cybersectors.com 2013-09-30

# Privacy Policy

**The privacy of our visitors is important to us.**

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our site, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files:-

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as BSNL or Airtel), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Email Address:-

This is a free content site and to prevent SPAM and to keep you always connected as a member we do require information from you (user name or password) to log-in and comment. We do not sell any information from our site to any outside party. The only e-mail sent from our websites is in response to an inquiry that you may send us or as a result of joining our double opt-in e-mail list. If anything comes to your attention which could potentially be a violation of this policy, please let us know immediately so that we can investigate it and try to correct it.

Cookies and Web Beacons:-

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a pop-up once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

Presently we don’t have any ads on our site & we may use third-party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing City real estate ads to someone in city, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing computer hardware/gadgets/cell-phones ads to someone who frequents to these sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Avira/ Bitdefender/ Kaspersky. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

As mentioned earlier we may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. This Website uses Google for advertisements

About Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the  **[Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)**.

For more information on  **[cookies visit here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx)**.

**Contact Person:**

Devagya Uikey (Admin & Support)  
devgaya@cybersectors.com
